[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
[PHILLIPA SCREAMS]
[SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
ATTENDANT [IN JAPANESE]:
Are you here to kill me?
I know what this is.
I've seen one before.
Many, many years ago.
It belonged to a man I met
in a half-remembered dream.
A man possessed
of some radical notions.
COBB:
What is the most resilient parasite?
A bacteria? A virus?
An intestinal worm?
ARTHUR:
Uh...
What Mr. Cobb is trying to say...
An idea.
Resilient. Highly contagious.
Once an idea has taken hold of the brain,
it's almost impossible to eradicate.
An idea that is fully formed,
fully understood, that sticks.
Right in there somewhere.
For someone like you to steal?
Yes. In the dream state,
your conscious defenses are lowered...
...and that makes your thoughts
vulnerable to theft.
It's called extraction.
Mr. Saito, we can train
your subconscious to defend itself...
...from even the most skilled extractor.
How can you do that?
Because I am the most skilled extractor.
I know how to search your mind
and find your secrets. I know the tricks.
And I can teach them to you,
so that even when you're asleep...
...your defense is never down.